<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<en-GB>

<name>League Preferences Administration</name>
<menu-lge>League Preferences</menu-lge>
<help>Using the league prefences league and global administrators can change some of the settings for a league without modifying the PHP files.</help>

<lname>League</lname>

<prime_title>&lt;b&gt;Primary Tournament&lt;/b&gt;</prime_title>
<prime_help>The primary tournament is used for the front page league table</prime_help>

<second_title>&lt;b&gt;Secondary Tournament&lt;/b&gt;</second_title>
<second_help>The secondary tournament is used for front page player performance stats</second_help>

<league_name_title>&lt;b&gt;League Name&lt;/b&gt;</league_name_title>
<league_name_help>Name of your league</league_name_help>

<forum_url_title>&lt;b&gt;Forum URL&lt;/b&gt;</forum_url_title>
<forum_url_help>The link to use in the Forum button on the main menu. Leave this blank for no forum.</forum_url_help>

<welcome_title>&lt;b&gt;Welcome Message&lt;/b&gt;</welcome_title>
<welcome_help>Message to appear at the top of the home page. This can be HTML.</welcome_help>

<rules_title>&lt;b&gt;League Rules&lt;/b&gt;</rules_title>
<rules_help>The rules to display under the Rules menu. This can be HTML.</rules_help>


<submit_text>Save</submit_text>
<submit_title>Update this league`s preferences</submit_title>

<failedSave>Unable to save preferences</failedSave>
<failedValidate>Oh Noes! The league administration module has failed the ptid!=stid check.  Please alert your administrator!</failedValidate>
<failedSave>Sorry, you don't have permission to update this league</failedSave>

<saved>Updated</saved>

<css_title>&lt;b&gt;League CSS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;i&gt;(careful if you don't know CSS)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You may need to clear cache after editing.</css_title>
<css_help>You can theme your League, but you need to know CSS!</css_help>

<core_theme_title>&lt;b&gt;Core Theme&lt;/b&gt;</core_theme_title>
<core_theme_help>These are pre-built themes you can use, or build from using the League CSS below.</core_theme_help>

<tv_title>&lt;b&gt;Initial Treasury&lt;/b&gt;</tv_title>
<tv_help>Usually set this to 1000000, but you can pick other values.</tv_help>

<tv_sevens_title>&lt;b&gt;Sevens Initial Treasury&lt;/b&gt;</tv_sevens_title>
<tv_sevens_help>Usually set this to 600000, but you can pick other values.</tv_sevens_help>

<language_title>&lt;b&gt;Language&lt;/b&gt;</language_title>
<language_help>Your leagues default language.</language_help>

<teams_legend_title>&lt;b&gt;Teams of Legend/Optional Rosters&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Disable old rosters from the team creation page.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;(does not interfere with teams already created)&lt;/i&gt;</teams_legend_title>
<teams_legend_help>Tick a team box to disable that team from being available on the team creation page: Ticked box = Disabled.</teams_legend_help>
<teams_legend_amazon>Amazon (Teams of Legend)</teams_legend_amazon>
<teams_legend_helf>High Elf (Teams of Legend)</teams_legend_helf>
<teams_legend_chorf>Chaos Dwarf (Teams of Legend)</teams_legend_chorf>
<teams_legend_vamps>Vampire (Teams of Legend)</teams_legend_vamps>
<teams_legend_khemri>Tomb Kings (Teams of Legend)</teams_legend_khemri>
<teams_legend_slann>Slann (Optional NAF roster)</teams_legend_slann>

<dungeonbowl_title>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dungeon Bowl Team Rosters&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Disable Dungeon Bowl team rosters from the team creation page.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;(does not interfere with teams already created)&lt;/i&gt;</dungeonbowl_title>
<dungeonbowl_help>Tick the box to disable Dungeon Bowl teams from being available on the team creation page: Ticked box = Disabled.</dungeonbowl_help>
<dungeonbowl>Dungeon Bowl Teams</dungeonbowl>

<sevens_title>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sevens Team Rosters&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Disable Sevens team rosters from the team creation page.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;(does not interfere with teams already created)&lt;/i&gt;</sevens_title>
<sevens_help>Tick the box to disable Sevens teams from being available on the team creation page: Ticked box = Disabled.</sevens_help>
<sevens>Sevens Teams</sevens>

<megastars_title>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mega-Stars&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Disable Mega-Stars from inducements.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;(see latest FAQ for list of which Star Players are classed as Mega-Stars)&lt;/i&gt;</megastars_title>
<megastars_help>Tick the box to disable Mega-Stars from being available on inducements: Ticked box = Disabled.</megastars_help>
<megastars>Mega-Stars</megastars>

<randomskillrolls_title>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;Automated Random Skills Generator&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Disable Automated Random Skill option from Team Management Box.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;(do not disable this unless you enable Manual Random Skill Entry below)&lt;/i&gt;</randomskillrolls_title>
<randomskillrolls_help>Tick the box to disable Automated Random Skills from being available on the team management Box, in which case only Random Skill Manual Entry will be allowed: Ticked box = Disabled.</randomskillrolls_help>
<randomskillrolls>Automated Random Skills</randomskillrolls>

<randomskillmanualentry_title>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;Manual Random Skill Entry&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Disable Manual Random Skill Entry from the Roster/team page.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;(do not disable this unless you enable Automated Random Skill Rolls above)&lt;/i&gt;</randomskillmanualentry_title>
<randomskillmanualentry_help>Tick the box to disable Manual Random Skill Entry from being available on the Roster/Team Page, in which case only Automated Random Skill generation will be allowed: Ticked box = Disabled.</randomskillmanualentry_help>
<randomskillmanualentry>Manual Random Skill Entry</randomskillmanualentry>

<bonuspoints_title>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;Additional League Points&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Define what bonus points to use. They will be added automatically according to these rules.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;(must be used in conjunction with a Ranking System in the Tournament Manager that includes [bonus])&lt;/i&gt;</bonuspoints_title>
<bonuspoints_help>Define how many bonus points to award for Major Wins, Major Beatings and Clean Sheets. 
Entering 0 points for all three will hide the Additonal League points calculator on the Match Report.
</bonuspoints_help>
<major_win_tds>Major Win TDs = Major Win for scoring how many TDs? Set No of TDs here, usually 3.</major_win_tds>
<major_win_pts>Major Win Points = Bonus points earned for a Major Win, usually 1. Enter 0 to hide on Match report.</major_win_pts>
<clean_sheet_pts>Clean Sheet Points = Bonus points for conceding 0 TDs (clean sheet), usually 1. Enter 0 to hide on Match report.</clean_sheet_pts>
<major_beat_cas>Major Beating Casualties = Major Beating for scoring how many CAS? Set No of CAS here, usually 3.</major_beat_cas>
<major_beat_pts>Major Beating Points = Bonus points earned for a Major Beating, usually 1. Enter 0 to hide on Match report.</major_beat_pts>

</en-GB>
